[{"id": 2978, "question": "Deng Nannan, 15, used to hate drinking milk for breakfast. But she had to drink it because her mom, as well as many others, said that milk was good for her growing body. Besides, milk and bread made up a convenient diet that saved her parents a lot of time after Deng entered junior school and had to arrive at school early in the morning. After that, Mengniu and Yili became her favorite brands of morning milk and yoghurt after dinner. However, she has been forced to change her diet since the recent milk crisis. Many best-selling milk brands such as Mengniu, Yili and Bright were discovered to contain melamine , which is usually used to make plastic. The bad milk products have sickened more than 5,300 babies and killed four. \"I shifted to rice porridge,\" she said. \"My mom has to get up at 5:5...\n\nQ: According to the passage, why do some students stop drinking milk?", "options": ["Because their parents have enough time to prepare other foods for them", "Because they get tired of drinking the same type of milk.", "Because some harmful materials are found in some kinds of milk.", "Because milk becomes more and more expensive."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2297, "question": "Guide dogs are going to be available for the children who are unable to see normally in the UK for the first time, as the age limit is to be removed. The Guide Dogs for the Blind Association is to begin training dogs to help blind people under the age of 16. The association says too many youngsters with impaired eyesight are lacking in independence. They have only a limited social life because of their disability. Giving some of them guide dogs at a younger age is intended to help them to widen their range of activities and to improve their sense of self-confidence and independence. Guide dogs for these teenagers will begin to be provided from next year. There has been an experimental project to test the use of guide dogs with younger people. Charlotte, aged 14, was among the youngest guid...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the text?", "options": ["Blind people need guide dogs' assistance in their daily life.", "Age limit for the blind to have guide dogs is to be removed.", "More guide dogs will be trained in the UK.", "The project of using guide dogs is to begin."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1298, "question": "The latest fashion in kitchen is the food steamer. All the stores are selling them; everyone wants one. Steaming is one of the simplest and healthiest ways of cooking food.However, that cooking time is usually longer than with other methods. In case you're thinking of buying a steamer, I've done a survey about the steamers available on the market to help you decide which will suit you best. *Folding Steamer The simplest and least expensive is the folding stainless-steel version. Advantages: This is a good, basic design which sits inside a variety of different shapes of pans with the water under it; a ring in the center allows for easy lifting and it's easy to clean. Disadvantages: It only holds small dishes. Also, if you put too much water in the pan, it will boil up through the vegetables...\n\nQ: Why did the author carry out the survey?", "options": ["To inform people of different steamers", "To run an advertisement for steamers", "To find out a suitable steamer to buy", "To learn how to cook with steamers"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2235, "question": "A new international study shows that some people's biological clock plays a powerful role for their life expectancy, regardless of lifestyle choices. Published in the latest issue ofAgingon Wednesday, the study has found the most definitive evidence to explain why some people keep healthy lifestyle but die younger than others. Geneticist Steve Horvath from the University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), led a team of 65 scientists around the world to record age-related changes to human DNA, analyse blood samples collected from 13, 000 people and estimate their lifespan. A higher biological age, regardless of actual age, consistently predicts an earlier death, the study says. \"You get people who are vegan, sleep 10 hours a day, have a low-stress job, and still end up dying young,\" Horvath...\n\nQ: According to the study, it can be inferred that   _  .", "options": ["people who keep healthy lifestyle tend to live longer", "people's lifespan can be predicted by their age", "5 percent of people are believed to have a faster innate aging rate", "anti-aging interventions have proved to slow the innate aging rate"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1807, "question": "Who we are Shanghai Super Star provides combination service including translation and tourism and sourcing, focusing on interpreting and translation. Our professional team offer highly professional business interpreters, assistants, companions and exhibition translators and sourcing for a variety of business requirements as well as tour guides to first-time tourists coming to China. Why choose us ^ Our professional and experienced business interpreters/translators have more than 5 years' experience and also have professional education background like business, foreign trade, management etc. ^ Our knowledgeable and enthusiastic private tour guides are always ready to help design your unique trip. ^ Our reliable interpreters have solid experience in different industries. So we will be your g...\n\nQ: The two comments in the passage are intended to indicate    .", "options": ["Susan is very professional and can meet the needs of different customers", "American customers have a preference for Shanghai Super Star", "Shanghai Super Star enjoys a good reputation among customers", "Shanghai Super Star provides combination service for customers"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1282, "question": "When looking for love, people may go to some extreme lengths. They might go on blind dates set up by family and friends. They might write personal ad to place in newspapers. Or they might use a computer to help them in their search for a soul mate by joining an online dating service. Some people have even tried to find their perfect match through game shows on television. Many of these TV dating shows, including The Bachelor andWho Wants to Marry Multimillionaire?, have proved to be popular, with millions of viewers watching each week to find out which of the contestants will find true love. Of all these game shows, perhaps the one with the most unexpected ending was Mr. Right, which was shown in England in 2002. On the show, a bachelor, thirty-five-year-old Lance Gerrard-Wright, dated fif...\n\nQ: What happened after seven weeks of doing the show?", "options": ["All of the women won prizes.", "Lance asked one of the women to marry him.", "One of the women on the show started to cry.", "Ulrika asked Lance to marry her."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 861, "question": "Nathan's second-hand bike was good enough to get him anywhere he wanted to go. Of course, it couldn't match Tim's in a normal speed race, but all the fancy gears in the world wouldn't get you up Black Mountain. It was so steep in places that you had to get off your bike and push. On this particular afternoon, the odds were all on Nathan's side. First, he was stronger. Tim had always been thin, but recently he'd started to grow so fast that his arms and legs were like pieces of spaghetti. As well as being considerably fitter than his friend, Nathan knew the shortcuts up prefix = st1 /BlackMountain. So when Nathan accepted the challenge, he was sure he'd win. He nearly always did, in competitions with Tim. That was what was strange. Tim was so competitive, and yet he wasn't any good at physi...\n\nQ: It was sometimes quicker to use the tracks rather than the road because the   _  .", "options": ["tracks were partly hidden.", "tracks were easier to ride bikes on.", "road had many bends in it.", "road was overgrown after the winter."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1561, "question": "Two things changed my life: my mother and a white plastic bike basket. I have thought long and hard about it and it's true. I would be a different person if my mom hadn't turned a silly bicycle accessory into a life lesson I carry with me today. My mother and father were united in their way of raising children, but it mostly fell to my mother to actually carry it out. Looking back, I honestly don't know how she did it. Managing the family budget must have been a very hard task., but she made it look effortless. If we complained about not having what another kid did, we'd hear something like, \"I don't care what so -and -so got for his birthday, you are not getting a TV in your room a car for your birthday a lsvish sweet 16 party.\" We had to earn our allowance by doing chores around the hous...\n\nQ: When the author saw the basket in the window,she  _", "options": ["fell in love with it", "stared at her mother", "recognized it at once", "went up to the bike guy"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 997, "question": "It'll be an ordinary morning,like all the others.But instead of being woken up by the buzzing of an alarm clock, you'll be roused by the smell of freshly made coffee,light entering your room as the curtains open automatically,and a gentle back massage provided by your high-tech bed. This is what a typical person's life will be like two decades from now,according to The Guardian. Want to know more? After you get up,your apartment will be like an electronic orchestra with you as the conductor.With simple moves of your hand and spoken instructions,you'll be able to control your apartment's temperature,humidity,music and lighting.You'll be able to look through the day's news on translucent screens while your breakfast waits for you in the automatic oven. As you move into your kitchen,maybe you...\n\nQ: What might be the author's purpose in writing the text?", "options": ["To stress the iniportance of developing technology.", "To describe how advanced technologies will affect our future lives.", "To introduce one new invcnfion that will benefit our future lives.", "To remind people not to depend too much on computers."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 136, "question": "Dear Earthmen , I have enjoyed my stay on your interesting unusual planet. I think I understand the life on earth now and I would like to give you my impressions. First of all you live in boxes. Every morning you leave your big boxes and get into smaller boxes on wheels. All these small boxes race around and around, and finally stop to rest. You then leave these boxes on wheels and go to very large tall boxes. After testing all days you get back in your little boxes and return to your big boxes. There you sit and stare at tiny glowing boxes with moving pictures on the front. Only one thing puzzles me. One day I went to a football game. A bunch of angry boys fought over a little round ball. Everyone yelled for them to stop but they kept on fighting. They were angry, I suppose, about being c...\n\nQ: The small boxes on wheels are  _  .", "options": ["toys", "ears", "houses that can be moved", "boxes in which there are wheels"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 937, "question": "Shoppers who have cut back on purchases in the worrying U.S. economy are likely to continue their conservative shopping habits even if the economy improves, according to a new study. That signals continued bad news for retailers , who have been struggling to respond to a great cutback in spending as consumers have opened their wallets only for basic items, while cutting back on unimportant purchases. The report, which estimates retail sales growth to be flat this year, found that three-quarters of respondents to a monthly survey of 4,000 consumers said they had shifted their shopping behaviors because of the economy. Most said they were making do with less or going without some favorite items. \"The habits learned during this economic crisis have the potential to permanently change the mind...\n\nQ: The current shopping behavior in the US is becoming  _  .", "options": ["arbitrary", "protective", "conservative", "aggressive"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1954, "question": "Talking plants might sound like characters in a fairy tale. But recent scientific studies have shown that plants communicate with each other and with other living things in a surprising number of ways. To understand them, scientists say, we just have to learn their language. Farmers are especially interested in what plants have to say. \"Plants are able to communicate with all sorts of organisms . They can communicate with giant bacteria, with other plants and with insects. They do this chemically,\" said Cahill, an Ecology Professor of the University of Alberta in Canada. Plant scientists are just beginning to understand this chemical \"language\". Cahill says studies have shown, for example, that plants can evaluate conditions in their immediate environment and take appropriate actions. Plan...\n\nQ: When being eaten by an insect, the plant will   _  .", "options": ["walk away from trouble", "change its chemistry to kill the insect", "release a chemical vapor to \"ask\" other plants for help", "give off nice chemicals to attract friendly insects killing the pest"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1869, "question": "I recall a moment that I experienced with my dad when I was twenty-one. I was going to college and living with a couple of friends in Chicago. When the car I was using died, my dad, realizing that I needed transportation to get to work and to school, was good enough to lend me the money for a used car. Shortly after I bought it, my parents drove down to San Diego for the winter. Before they left, my dad gave me some of his bank deposit slips with clear and detailed instructions to put one hundred dollars of my earnings, every payday, into their savings account while they were gone. At that time of my life, I was not yet clear about what were the most important problems that I had to attend to first. I dismissed our agreement as nothing important and continued to spend my money as fast as I...\n\nQ: Which of the following do you think is the real cause of Dad's disappointment?", "options": ["The writer had not formed his fundamental values and principles.", "The writer had not thought clearly about his future.", "The writer had not made all the payments.", "The writer had spent too much money drinking in pubs."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 216, "question": "The Mysterious Universe By Ellen Jackson and Nic Bishop How did the universe begin? How big is it? What is dark matter? Cosmologist and expert supernova hunter Alex Filippenko hopes that supernovas can help us answer some of these questions. But first we've got to find them! Join Alex and his team as they go on the hunt with huge telescopes and banks of computers. The Time and Space of Uncle Albert By Russell Stannard What would you say if your uncle asked you whether you would like to go into space? You'd say, \"When do I leave?\", just like the girl in this story. Gedanken is speeding across the universe trying to help her uncle answer some questions, such as \"How big is space?\" and \"Where does gravity come from?\" Along the way she also discovers how to get heavier without getting fat, how...\n\nQ: What do the four books have in common?", "options": ["They have the same topics?", "They are intended for adults.", "They have the same number of characters", "They leave many questions to the readers"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2228, "question": "Thanksgiving Day was near. The first grade teacher gave her class a fun task----to draw a picture of something for which they were thankful. Most of the class would celebrate the holiday with turkey and other traditional goodies of season. These, the teacher thought, would be the subjects of her students' art. And they were. But Douglas made a different kind of picture. He drew a hand. Nothing else. Just an empty hand. Douglas was a different kind of boy. Most of the time, as other children played together, Douglas was likely to stand close by her side. Everyone could guess the pain he felt from his eyes. His picture interested other students. Whose hands could it be? One child guessed it was the hand of a farmer, because farmers raise turkeys. Another suggested a police officer, because t...\n\nQ: What did most students think of when given the task?", "options": ["Hand", "Turkey", "God", "Farmer"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3008, "question": "People bury treasure to stop other people from taking it. They choose a quiet place, dig a deep hole and bury the treasure in it. Then they make a map of where the treasure is or write down other clues that will help them or someone else to find it again. In Britain a few years ago, a writer wrote about some treasure that he had buried. He put clues in the story to help readers find it. Thousands of people hunted for the treasure. They dug holes all over Britain, hoping to find it. One of the most popular adventure stories ever written is Robert Louis Stephenson's \"Treasured Island\", an exciting story about a young boy, Jim Hawkins, who is captured by pirates and later finds some buried treasure. Then there is the true story about a man who had to travel overseas for a year. He did not tru...\n\nQ: From these stories we understand that    _    .", "options": ["we cannot trust banks.", "we should not trust anyone.", "a waterproof bag is not proof against worms and insects.", "insects eat anything."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3489, "question": "A family story is like a puzzle. Each family member leaves some clues. Family members come together because they have a common tie with one another, sharing a name and special traditions. Exploring family roots and sharing past memories ensure each tradition lives on. Ancestory.com has created customized \"Our Name is History\" books to give your family a look into your history by learning about your last name. By visiting _ , you can check if information is available for your last name. Ancestory.com researchers have collected more than 5 billion names from records such as passenger lists, immigration records and from birth, marriage and death records. The collected information is then used for each customized book. \"Our Name is History\" books are available for nearly 200,000 last names, ac...\n\nQ: What's the purpose of the author in writing this passage?", "options": ["To tell us how to explore family roots.", "To help family traditions to live on.", "To advertise \"Our Name is History\" books.", "To tell us how to create our own family history."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3444, "question": "It seems that the Englishman just cannot live without sports of some kind. A famous French humourist once said that this is because the English insist on behaving like children all their lives. Wherever you go in this country you will see both children and grown-ups knocking a ball about with a stick or something, as if in Britain men shall always remain boys and women girls! Still, it can never be bad to get exercise, can it? Taking all amateur and professional sports in Britain into consideration, there can be no doubt that football is at the top of the list. It is called soccer in the United States. The game originated in Britain and was played in the Middle Ages or even earlier, though as an organized game, or \"association football\", it dates only from the beginning of the 19th century...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following is NOT true about football and rugby?", "options": ["They differ in the shape of the ball", "They are played by different numbers of players", "They both can be handled", "They both can be kicked"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2411, "question": "Every language has its own special words and expressions. And a story can be told about each of them. \"Hot\" is a simple, easily-understood word. So are most of the expressions made with the word \"hot\". But not always, as we shall see. Take the phrase \"hot potato\" for example. The potato is a popular vegetable in the United States. Many people like baked potatoes, cooked in an oven or fire. Imagine trying to carry a hot, baked potato in your hand. It would be difficult, even painful, to do so. One such hot potato is taxes. Calling for higher taxes can mean defeat for a politician. And yet, if taxes are not raised, some very popular government programs could be cut, which can also make a politician very unpopular. Another expression is \"not so hot\". If you ask someone how she feels, she may ...\n\nQ: If you describe something as a hot potato, it   _  .", "options": ["is very popular", "has a high temperature", "is very difficult to deal with", "can't be held in your hand"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 252, "question": "They can be seen more frequently than ever before on college campuses, wearing thick-rimmed glasses while listening to indie music. One might find them playing unusual musical instruments, shopping at second-hand stores or expressing themselves in other unique ways. They call themselves hipsters. Being \"hip\" used to mean following the latest fashion. But gradually the word has evolved into a synonym for \"cool\". Hipsters value independent thinking, progressive politics, an appreciation of creativity and intelligence. Hipsters take pains and pride in not being mainstream. However, their culture has become quite trendy. This irony is central to their culture and offers an interesting paradox. \"I do take things in the mainstream with a grain of salt,\" says Ben Polson, a college student at Brow...\n\nQ: When Leopold said \"It's kind of the trend these days; everyone wants to be hip so no one's hip\", we can see that she felt a bit   _  .", "options": ["happy", "disappointed", "excited", "content"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1727, "question": "When we see well, we do not think about our eyes very often. It is only when we cannot see perfectly that we realize how important our eyes are. People who are near-sighted can only see things that are very close to their eyes. Everything else seems blurry (unclear). Many people who do a lot of work, such as writing, reading and sewing become near--sighted. People who are far-sighted _ from just the opposite problem. They can see things that are far away, but they have difficulty in reading a book unless they hold it at arm's length. If they want to do much reading, they must get glasses, too. Other people do not see clearly because their eyes are not exactly the right shape. They have what is called astigmatism . This, too, can be corrected by glasses. Some people's eyes become cloudy bec...\n\nQ: . When things far away seem indistinct  , one is probably  _  .", "options": ["near-sighted", "far-sighted", "astigmatic", "suffering from cataracts"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3403, "question": "My mother, Marisol Torres, came with her family to Australia in the early 1960s. Then my parents' marriage ended and Mum began the study of precious stones. Her interest in opals took her to the New South Wales remote town of Lightning Ridge. There were no luxuries , but she was closer to nature and had a chance to find black opals and make some money. My mother was beautiful with dark hair and brown eyes, but she was also quiet and shy. Early in the Ridge years, she kept to herself, but later, she started going to the neighbourhood centre to make friends. It was her dream to mine, but her get-rich-quick thinking was unrealistic. She was cheated and she was never very successful. But she kept a sense of humour and a charming smile. Then, just as friendships began to blossom, she was diagno...\n\nQ: What made the author's mother go to Lightning Ridge?", "options": ["The luxurious life there.", "Her new marriage there.", "Her interest in opals.", "Her passion for nature. ."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2944, "question": "Johnson went to Penquay for the weekend. He arrived there late on Friday evening. The landlady of the guest house, Mrs. Smith, answered the door and showed him to his room. Johnson was very tired and went straight to bed. He slept well and didn't wake up until nine o'clock the next morning. Johnson went downstairs for breakfast. Because there were no other guests, Mrs. Smith invited him to have breakfast with her family. Her only daughter, Catherine, about 13, was already sitting in the dining-room. Mrs. Smith went to the kitchen to prepare breakfast. Johnson noticed there were four places at the table and asked Catherine if there was another guest. Catherine told him that it was an empty place. And it used to be her father's place. Her father had been a fisherman. Three years before he ha...\n\nQ: Who was the tall man with a black beard?", "options": ["Another guest.", "Catherine's father.", "A friend of the family.", "Johnson's enemy."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1122, "question": "Last week, I bought an alarm system for about $ 450. It consisted of a control unit with three other small units. I put the control unit in the sitting room and fastened the other units by the front door, back door and living-room windows. The instructions told us to choose three numbers, so we chose 491, the last three numbers of our telephone number. Now I must explain how the alarm works: 1. There is a power siren in the control unit. It makes a very loud noise. 2. Each of the small units sends out beams or rays in different directions. If anything moves, it breaks a beam. This sends a signal to the control unit. The siren makes a noise that you can hear 50 meters away. 3. When we go to bed, I press the three buttons numbered 4, 9 and 1. Then we have 30 seconds to get out of the room be...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the passage?", "options": ["A burglar broke into the writer's house.", "The writer's wife was attacked by the burglar.", "The alarm that the writer bought must be made in Europe.", "It was a lizard that broke into the writer's house."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1555, "question": "There have been many great inventions, which have changed the way we live. The first great invention was one that is still very important today---the wheel. This made it easier to carry heavy things to travel long distances. For hundreds of years there were few inventions that have made as much effect as the wheel. There was little unknown land left in the world. People didn't have to explore much any more. They began to work to make life better instead. In the second half of the 19th century many great inventions were made. Among them were the camera, the electric light and the radio. These all became a big part of our life today. The first part of the 20th century saw more great inventions. The helicopter in 1909. Sound movies in 1926. The computer in 1928, and jet planes in 1930. This w...\n\nQ: Which of the following was turned out nearly at the same time with the jet plane?", "options": ["The radio.", "The camera.", "Nylon.", "The helicopter."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2862, "question": "The sunflower plant bears bright yellow flowers that always face the sun, hence the name. However, the plant is grown not only for its beautiful flowers, but also for its oil that has a host of health benefits. Sunflower oil prevents diseases, lowers cholesterol levels, keeps the heart healthy, and even prevents certain forms of cancer. Sunflower oil is a kind of \"magic oil\" when it comes to skin care, as it makes your skin soft and smooth, and prevents signs of aging. So, let us know more about its effects on your skin. 1. It Acts as an Effective Emollient . Sunflower oil is an effective emollient, which means that it helps the skin retain moisture. Thus, people with dry skin can benefit immensely from the regular use of the oil. Also, it is mild, and provides relief from irritation and i...\n\nQ: What are the functions of vitamin E?", "options": ["To make ultraviolet rays and beta-carotene.", "To stop sunburn and treat skin cancers.", "To protect skin and slow the pace of aging.", "To produce wrinkles and make skin bright."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3392, "question": "Little Tom down the street calls our dog \"The keep dog\".Zip is a sheep dog. But when Tom tries to say\" Seep\", it comes out \"keep\". And in a way Tom is right. Zip is always bringing things home for us to keep! I'll tell you about some of them. Zip's first present was a shoe. It was made of green silk. We didn't know how Zip found the shoe. But after a moment Mary, my big sister, told me the shoe had a strange smell. I nodded and held my nose. \"What do you think it is?\" \"It smells like something for cleaning. I think someone tried to clean a spot off the shoe. Then he put it at the door to dry.\" \"Along came Zip. And good-bye shoe!\" I said.\"We should take it back.\" \"We can't \".said my sistter. \"Maybe little Tom is right,\" Mary said. \"Maybe Zip is a keep dog!\"...\n\nQ: We can know from the reading that the dog   _  .", "options": ["likes to give presents to people", "has been kept in at the writer's home", "has brought some trouble", "likes to be called \"the keep dog\""], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2161, "question": "*1. Malan Flower: China Children's Art Theatre stages a fairy tale musical \"Malan Flower\" this weekend. Beautiful Malan flowers were blossoming everywhere on Malan Mountain, and hard-working girl Xiao Lan was married to the god of flowers, Ma Lang. They lived a happy life in harmony with Grandpa Tree. and all the lovely little animals. However, greedy Old Cat made use of the jealousy of elder sister Da Lan to kill Xiao Lan, in an attempt to keep the magic Malan flower under her possession. This fairy tale entertained three generations of Chinese youth. Time: 7: 30 p. m., until August 21 Place: The Great Theatre of the Cultural Palace of the Nationalities, west of Xidan Area Tel: 6602-2530 *2. Joyful jugglers: The China Acrobatic Troupe is staging a nightly variety show at the Tiandi Theatr...\n\nQ: Which advertisement will Michael be most interested in if he likes fairy tales?", "options": ["Malan Flower.", "Joyful jugglers.", "Tour of love.", "Army artist."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1619, "question": "Your children's teacher will be providing extra time for test preparation. This school year's test will be held on January 8 and 9. The test preparation time is open to all students, and we strongly encourage your children to attend. This year we are changing the time for our test preparation: it will be on Thursday mornings from 8:10 to 8:50. This helps children who ride the bus and cannot stay for the after-school period. It also helps avoid conflicts with after-school activities. Danielle and Marina will be working with the recent new test takers 6 days on the following Thursdays: 15th, Nov; 29th, Nov; 6th, Dec; 13th, Dec.; 20th, Dec. and 3rd, Jan. Besides the test preparation lectures on these dates, teachers are already putting test preparation into their usual courses. We are finding...\n\nQ: The time for test preparation has been changed to   _  .", "options": ["make it more convenient for the students to attend", "help the new test-takers have more time to read", "avoid disagreement in time between different years of students", "avoid conflicts between preparation time and the usual courses"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 448, "question": "Good Teachers A language training school at Yayuncun needs two full-time teachers and three part-time teachers to teach adults, 12 students a class, oral English and business English during afternoons and evenings. Full-time teachers 25--30 hours per week, 10 000--2 000 yuan per month. Part-time teachers can choose the class to teach, 100--150 yuan per hour, according to your experience. Need native English speakers with teaching experience. Please send your RESUME and PICTURE to eslchina@ yahoo.com.cn Writers/Researchers Currently, Fisher's Travel SOS is looking for the freelance writer and researcher with experience in journalism and the ability to computers, it is part-time positions for our project that will take a month to complete. Work is conducted at home, and will take a couple of...\n\nQ: All the following are necessary as a researcher EXCEPT that  _", "options": ["you are able to use the computer", "you should be interested in the job", "you can work several hours a day", "you must finish your work every day"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2112, "question": "The landmark success of herbal expert Tu Youyou, the first Chinese woman national to win a Nobel prize in science, hasaroused an extreme sense of national pride and hopes on the future of traditional Chinese medicine (TCM). Tu, born in 1930, shared the 2015 Nobel Prize for Physiology or Medicine with Irish-born William Campbell and Japan's Satoshi Omura for her discoveries concerning a therapy against malaria. She discovered Artemisinin , a drug that has significantly reduced thedeath rates for patients suffering from malaria . \"Artemisinin is a gift for the world people from the traditional Chinese medicine. It is of great importance for curing malaria and other infectious diseases and for protecting the health of the world people,\" Tu said in Beijing. \"The discovery of Artemisinin is a s...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that Artemisinin has a good effect on   _   .", "options": ["reducing the death rates of cancer patients.", "curing patients suffering from malaria.", "declining the infection rates of diseases.", "preventing people from being infected with malaria."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1315, "question": "The Isle of Wight, off the south coast of England, is the best place in Europe for discovering dinosaur bones. Dinosaur Farm Museum was established in 1993. Since then, the museum has introduced the study of old bones to many more people. What we offer Visitors can enjoy our displays, or watch us cleaning dinosaur bones and other fossils found on the island's beaches. The museum has a variety of different fossils, many of them never displayed to the public before. As more are discovered all the time, you can be sure of seeing something new each time you visit. We have a free Fossil Identification Service, so you can bring in any fossils you have and find out what they are. In addition, we have a reasonably-priced Museum Shop, where you can buy a souvenir of your visit. You could also bring...\n\nQ: Which of the following is free of charge at the museum?", "options": ["Food for a picnic.", "Attending fossil hunts.", "Having fossils identified.", "A souvenir of the museum."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1852, "question": "Depressed people can be very difficult to be around,and yet they need more than the usual amount of support and understanding from their friends and family. The anger and lack of concern that a depressed person may have for people close to him or her can be very disturbing to someone who's trying to help.At such times,the sincerity of a friend or a family member is questioned when the depressed person doesn't feel worthy of someone's friendship.Withdrawal from others can make it nearly impossible to encourage a depressed person to enter into activities that may help pull him or her out of the depression. It is frequently difficult for a depressed person to carry on a conversation.Attempts to help may be met with defensiveness and verbal attacks.While being supportive and understanding,the ...\n\nQ: What are you advised to say to a depressed person?", "options": ["Try to look happy and you'll be better.", "I know exactly how you feel.", "I had a similar experience.And it might help you.", "Cheer up and get rid of your depression."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2741, "question": "Occasionally, my father came back drunk. Late at night, he beat on the door, pleading to my mother to open it .He was on his way home from drinking, gambling, or some combination thereof, misspending money that we could have used and wasting time that we desperately needed. It was the late-1970s. My parents were separated. My mother was now raising a group of boys on her own. My father spouted off about what he planned to do for us, buy for us.In fact, he had no intention of doing anything. As a father who was supposed to love us, in fact, he lacked the understanding of what it truly meant to love a child--or to hurt one. To him, this was a harmless game that kept us excited and begging. In fact, it was a cruel, corrosive lie. I lost faith in his words and in him. I wanted to stop caring, ...\n\nQ: From the passage, the father was  _   in the writer's memory.", "options": ["selfish and cruel", "proud and cold", "imperfect but loving", "shy but thoughtful"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 47, "question": "A new law helps people with disabilities. The law says that people with disabilities must be able to get into and out of all public buildings. It also says that business must offer special services to people who have special needs. Companies can not refuse to hire disabled workers. Many businesses may have to change their buildings and services. --Ramps must be built so people can get into buildings. --Movie theatres must have space for people in wheelchairs and seats for their friends to sit near them. --Elevators must have floor number in _ . This law will help millions of people. One woman who has been in a wheelchair for many years said, \"It is like a dream.\"...\n\nQ: The word \"Braille\" means_.", "options": ["words known by foreigners", "words known by common people", "words on walls", "words known by the blind"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 246, "question": "Worn by the rich and famous around the world and now a $799.04 million-a-year enterprise , Ugg boots have come a long way since their 1973 creation--designed to keep surfers' feet warm in cold Australian conditions. Twenty-eight years after selling the rights to his woollen-lined creation, Aussie Ugg boot inventor Shane Stedman says he has no regrets though missing out on a great footwear fortune . A lifelong surfer, Mr. Stedman, now 69, who lives at beachside Mona Vale in Sydney, said his invention grew from need. \"The sea is bloody cold in the Aussie winter...I used to wear football jerseys to keep them (feet) warm\", Mr. Stedman said. But his sheepskin invention soon solved the problem and Mr. Stedman went on to spend a decade selling the sturdy boots, until 1983 when he sold the rights ...\n\nQ: Ugg boots were invented by   _  .", "options": ["Mona Vale.", "Stedman.", "Deckers.", "An American surfer."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1325, "question": "City farms are gaining popularity in cities and towns around the United States. City Farms in Edmonston, Maryland, is located near shopping centers, car repair shops and homes. The neighborhood is a working-class community. People do not have very much money, and they have limited access to fresh food in markets. Over the past two years, the farm has attracted volunteers from the community like Marcy Clark. She schools her four children at home. On a recent day she brought them to Eco City Farms for a lesson. Alston Clark thinks his experience very valuable. \"I like coming out here, \"he says, \"You know, you connect with the earth, where your food comes from. You appreciate the food a little bit more. \" Margaret Morgan-Hubbard started Eco City Farms. She thinks of it as a place where people...\n\nQ: City farms are close to the following places EXCEPT    .", "options": ["shopping centers", "car repair shops", "working-class community", "fast-food restaurants"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2979, "question": "Deng Nannan, 15, used to hate drinking milk for breakfast. But she had to drink it because her mom, as well as many others, said that milk was good for her growing body. Besides, milk and bread made up a convenient diet that saved her parents a lot of time after Deng entered junior school and had to arrive at school early in the morning. After that, Mengniu and Yili became her favorite brands of morning milk and yoghurt after dinner. However, she has been forced to change her diet since the recent milk crisis. Many best-selling milk brands such as Mengniu, Yili and Bright were discovered to contain melamine , which is usually used to make plastic. The bad milk products have sickened more than 5,300 babies and killed four. \"I shifted to rice porridge,\" she said. \"My mom has to get up at 5:5...\n\nQ: Which of the following milk brands wasn't discovered to contain melamine?", "options": ["Sanyuan", "Yili", "Mengniu", "Bright"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2303, "question": "Some diaries from Jackie Chan's blog January 4, 2009 Lately I've been busy in Beijing having meetings to discuss my new movie. I also attended John Wu's ceremony of his new movie,Red Cliff,which took two years to complete. I'm good friends with the director John Wu and the main actor Tony Leung. January 5, 2009 Today I went to record a television program for Beijing TV calledVolunteers Across China. This TV program is a large-scale reality show that is based on the idea that \"good people reap good rewards\" and it hopes to encourage people to be more aware and help the \"good people\" who are in difficult situations. January 6, 2009 I'm very pleased to _ that my Jackie Chan automobile website is set up and officially operating! I hope that through this automotive website, I can get in touch w...\n\nQ: With whom does the author sing the songZhongguo Nian ?", "options": ["John Wu.", "Tony Leung.", "Chang Shilei.", "Tan Jing."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2409, "question": "Wang Lu, 24, one of many students studying abroad who'll come home for work, majors in business & management studies at Edinburgh's Napier University. She had planned what to do after graduation in the UK: two years' work experience at a restaurant and a tour around Europe. But now her plans are up in the air. Following the UK Home Secretary's meeting on reform of the student immigration system, the UK government recently announced the end of the post-study work visa from April 2012. This will force tens of thousands of Chinese students to leave the UK after graduation. Sadly, the domestic job market doesn't welcome them with open arms. A report by Tigtag.com at the end of 2011 showed that over 35 percent of students admitted that they have employment problems. \"Returning students often ha...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the text that   _  .", "options": ["the reform of immigration system has great effects on the British people", "some practices like eating snacks are allowed at the workplace in China", "lack of work experience is a big problem to find a suitable job in the UK", "returning students are expected to adapt to the new working environment"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1337, "question": "A cheap drug that can stop bleeding in people recently injured in an accident could potentially save the lives of tens of thousands worldwide, a new study says. Researchers studied the effects of tranexamic acid , or TXA, in more than 10,000 injured people in 40 countries who received the drug within 8 hours of being injured. The study was published in the medical journalLancet.Doctors found that patients who got TXA had a 15percent lower chance of dying from _ than those who didn't get it . They also had a 10 percent lower chance of dying from any other cause, including organ failure and a head injury. The study was paid for by the British government. The drug is commonly used in wealthy countries during elective surgeries to stop bleeding , but isn't used for accident victims. TXA is off...\n\nQ: What can we learn about TXA from the passage?", "options": ["It can only be made in England", "It was only used in operations before", "It is a patented drug", "It is mainly used in poor countries"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3306, "question": "In the 19thcentury, Americans from the eastern states moved out west to settle in the rich new lands along the Pacific Coast. The most difficult part of their trip was crossing \"the Great American Desert\" in the western part of the United States by horse and wagon. The western desert can be very dangerous. There is little water and there are few trees. But the desert also has scenery of great beauty. Tall towers of red and yellow stone rise sharply from the flat, sandy valley floor. The scene has been photographed many times and appears in movies and on TV. In Arizona, man-made dams across the Colorado River have made two large lakes in the middle of the dry desert country. At Lake Powell, the red stone arch of Rainbow Bridge rises high above the blue lake. There are few roads. Many areas ...\n\nQ: From this passage. we can conclude that  _  .", "options": ["the western desert is a good place for people to live in", "there is little water but there are many trees in the desert", "the desert is dangerous but it is full of beauty", "till now, people know little about the desert"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2505, "question": "Dave Bruno works as an online marketing manager. Several years ago, one weekend Bruno and his family did a major house cleanup and then donated several bags of unneeded items to the local Goodwill store. \"After all were done, I looked around and realized that I still had too much stuff\", says Bruno, \" _ \" That realization prompted the 39-year-old father of three to try an experiment, \"The 100Thing Challenge\". With the goal of breaking free of what he calls a \"bad habit of consumerism , Bruno was determined to live for one year with just 100 personal items. He cut down his possessions to 94 items, including a Bible, laptop, guitar, wedding ring, car and clothes. He created some guidelines for the experiment since his wife and daughters did not participate, familyshared and household items d...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Live with 100 Things", "Defeat 100 Challenges in Life", "Survive by Your Motto", "Consume for Consumption's Sake"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1414, "question": "Some children are natural-born bosses. They have a strong need to make decisions, manage their environment, and lead rather than follow. Stephen Jackson, a Year One student, \"operates under the theory of what's mine is mine and what's yours is mine,\" says his mother. \"The other day I bought two new Star Wars light sabers . Later, I saw Stephen with the two new ones while his brother was using the beat-up ones. \" \"Examine the extended family, and you'll probably find a bossy grandparent, aunt, uncle or cousin in every generation. It's an inheritable trait,\" says Russell Barkley, a professor at the Medical University of South Carolina. Other children who may not be particularly bossy can gradually gain dominance when they sense their parents are weak, hesitant, or in disagreement with each o...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about?", "options": ["How bossy behavior can be controlled.", "How we can get along with bossy children.", "What leads to children's bossy behavior.", "What effect bossy behavior brings about."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 357, "question": "America's child movie star Shirley Temple Black died late Monday evening at the age of 85. Her fans in China are also deeply saddened. Temple is just one example of movie stars that China adored, and still adores. Here's our editor's pick of the top movie stars who have influenced China. 1. Sylvester Stallone Oh, Rambo! The first strong American man that China knew. His accented English, easily recognizable even for someone who doesn't speak English, and his eyes that never seemed to smile, makes him someone whom cannot be forgotten. He represented the strong American image, and even stirred a boxing and bodybuilding fever in China. 2.Charlie Chaplin (April 16, 1889 - December 25, 1977) In the 20th century, it is not too much to say that Einstein made the greatest contributions to science,...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the passage?", "options": ["Sylvester Stallone taught boxing and bodybuilding and caused a fever in China.", "Charlie Chaplin was China's close friend because he introduced comedy to China.", "Audrey Hepburn's movie made the Mouth of Truth and the Spanish Steps popular.", "Shirley Temple's works can only help Americans forget hardships and enjoy life better."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 509, "question": "I am so worried about global warming. We need stop cutting down all of the trees so that they can absorb the carbon dioxide. I think the Kyoto Protocol to stop pollution is a great idea ,and I hope our country will decide to follow it, too.[: http://wx.jtyjy.com/] -- Eli S.,10,Texa People should do all they can to help stop pollution, even if it is something as little as recycling your soda can. Every little thing helps. Maybe schools can put recycling bins in classrooms. Students can bring in all of their cans and bottles and see how many the school can collect. -- Lindsey A.,11, Massachusett[: http://wx.jtyjy.com/.Com] The United States should take action to help stop pollution. Since we are one of the richest countries, we should at least spend a little money to help. -- Aaron z,11,Mass...\n\nQ: What do the six children mainly talk about?", "options": ["Environmental problems.", "The Kyoto Protocol.", "Animal protection.", "The climate change."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2755, "question": "In summer, millions of people will head for the beach.And while the ocean can be a great place to swim and play, it may also be useful in another way.Some scientists think that waves could help make electricity. \"Have you ever been on a surfboard or boat and felt yourself being lifted up by a wave? Or have you jumped in the water and felt the energy as waves crashed over you?\" asked Jamie Taylor of the Wave Energy Group at the University of Edinburgh in Scotland.\"There is certainly a lot of energy in waves.\" Scientists are working on using that energy to make electricity. Most waves are created when winds blow across the ocean.\"The winds start out by making little ripples in the water, but if they keep on blowing , those ripples get bigger and bigger and turn into waves, \"Taylor said.\"Wave...\n\nQ: What can be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["How to Get Electricity by Waves.", "A Huge Resource of Energy.", "Can Waves Make Electricity?", "The Disadvantages of Wave Energy."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2406, "question": "Another of President Bush's critics on climate change and his former rival for the White House, Al Gore, is inprefix = st1 /Londonon Friday to launch an environmental project with the head of the Virgin Business Company, Richard Branson. They're announcing a multi-million dollar international prize to encourage development and research into new forms of low carbon technology. The prize will be available to anyone who can apply a successful method of removing large amounts of carbon dioxide from the atmosphere. Almost all scientists agree that we are experiencing global warming due to increased amounts of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere. Carbon dioxide is released when fuel is burned. Oil, coal and wood are all fuels that release the gas. When biological wasted breaks down, it also release...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["We should pay more attention to the solution to an environmental problem", "An project is launched to award those who can find ways to solve an environmental problem.", "Al Gore is going to present a prize to the person who can solve an environmental problem.", "A lot of people will apply methods to solve an environmental problem."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2193, "question": "Trans-Bridge Tours is looking forward to providing you with another year of exciting One-Day travel destinations in 2016. Statue of Liberty & Ellis Island August 15 (Sat) $78 Adult; $66 Child (4-12); $ 75 Senior (62+) No visit to the New York City area is complete without a trip to the world's most famous landmarks--- the Statue of Liberty and Ellis Island. Price includes transportation to Liberty State Park and timed ferry tickets. 9/11 Museum& Memorial September 29 (Tue) $ 87 Adult; $ 78 Youth (7-17); Senior $80(65+) The Museum displays artifacts associated with the events of 9/11, while presenting stories of loss and recovery. The Memorial between the twin reflecting pools, is a tribute of remembrance and honor to the nearly 3,000 people killed in the terror attacks. The New York Botani...\n\nQ: Which of the following charges an adult the lowest fee?", "options": ["Statue of Liberty & Ellis Island", "9/11 Museum & Memorial", "The New York Botanical Garden", "Hagley Museum & Winterthur"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 132, "question": "This girl is almost without shelter. She may not realize it, but she's more exposed to the world than she's ever likely to be again. And it isn't because she's a girl. It could be a boy. It could be you. But why is she 'shelter less ? She s got a place to live in quite a pleasant place by the look of it and if shelter . Doesn't' t mean a house, then what does it mean? When we say someone \"lives a sheltered life\" , we don't only mean that their house is comfortable. We mean that they're protected from too many worries and troubles, that they live in a settled home, probably surrounded by friends and family, and that they don't have to cope with the difficulties the world is full of alone. Certainly no one would say that this girl was leading a sheltered life; she's leaving home to earn her ...\n\nQ: What would be best title for the passage?", "options": ["Leaving Home", "Finding a House", "Living with the Family", "Making a Better Shelter"], "answer": 0}]